Ending
Hello. This is Kakihara from Nogizaka46.
Today, the woman who was loved by 8 did Exit 8.
Yes, I have been an idol since my debut as a woman loved by 8,
I was born on August 8, and my attendance number is usually 8,
I was born on August 8, my attendance number is usually 8, and my entry number for the audition is 18,
I was born on August 8, my attendance number is usually 8, and my audition entry number is 18, and I have had a strong connection with the number 8 in my life,
And when I saw that Exit 8 had been released, I knew I had to do it,
When I saw that Exit 8 had been released, I thought I had no choice but to do it, and I wanted everyone to witness how a woman loved by 8 exits from Exit 8,
I would like you all to witness the woman who is loved by the 8s leave through Exit 8, so I am going to do it.
I'm in the sky now, by the way, and I requested this.
I'm actually a green bag, but you said I could do anything I wanted,
I thought if I'm going underground now, I might as well stay in the sky.
I wonder how it's going. I wonder what's going on now.
What's going on? But I'm in the sky.
Let me tell you what the game is about.
You are trapped in an endless underground passageway.
Keep an eye out for anything out of the ordinary.
If you find something strange, turn around immediately.
If you don't find anything strange, don't turn around
Go out from Exit 8.
These are the four points.
It's a simple game.
So it's like finding a mistake.
So I'd like to go out from exit 8.
Ah!
Oh!
Huh?
Ah!
Like this.
Oh!
That's great.
Footsteps.
I kind of wanted to do this.
I was trying not to watch the play-by-play video or anything, but
I was in too much and I couldn't have a little meeting.
That's why I'm doing this uncle thing.
Good morning.
So that's how it is.
Tang.
Well, this...
It means there's going to be an anomaly here.
So I have to memorize all this?
What?
That's a lot.
No smoking.
And there's exit 8.
Oh, my God, there's only 8. That's my birthday sign! Oh, my gosh!
with a smile... I wonder if I'll have to remember that one too.
I don't know how much I need to remember.
Part-time part-timer wanted!
I can't remember all the letters
6:00 to 10:00
Cute!
Four-way bibliography
Stylish posters
Make-up Art
Photo Exhibition
Cute
Move Fest
General Sales October 10
What?
3,000 yen
Oh!
Bohan camera working. Where?
Oh, this is it.
Oh, yeah.
Ah, the underground plaza.
So, is this... is this... is this place empty now?
Is this the way to go?
Let's go. So, this, this, this, oh, this is how we're going to run?
Oh. Why are we running, do we need something?
Please keep to the left. Yes, sir.
What's this? Oh, zero.
Will there be more from here?
Nambu Park.
Yahoppongi Intersection, eh.
Wow, Roppongi has become Happongi. Oh, does it start here? Huh?
Heh heh heh, YEN? I have to find it, from here. Yes, sir.
What?
What's wrong?
No smoking.
August 8th hasn't changed, Pops.
You haven't changed.
Mmm-hmm.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Can you please step aside?
Hey, Uncle Tsushin
Is this different? What's different?
Electricity board room
Oh, is this part changed too? If you told me the size of these squares, I would never understand.
It was October 10, it's art, it's a bibliography of methods, and it's open.
Eh, I don't think it's changed.
Employees only, cleaners, stuffed books.
What?
So much? This is different?
If there's nothing unusual, we can go on, right?
Huh? Huh? Huh? Zero?
Hmm? Hmm? You mean there's something wrong?
What? Where, where, where, where? What? Where?
Oh, I'm back.
Nothing's changed since the last time I saw you.
Nothing's changed.
Aah! Your face!
What? My uncle's face!
Aww!
What?
Huh?
Whoa! Oh, my God! What? It's so buggy!
Toumei, your uncle's face is turning East. This is strange. This is strange. This is strange.
There's something wrong. There's something wrong!
Ah! Here it comes! One, one, one, one!
Finally! That's what it feels like!
That's what we're supposed to look for. The more you throw, the more you find.
Okay. Oh!
I see it now. I see it now. It's all makeup artists.
All make-up artists. Odd.
Odd... ah... ah... ah... ah... ah... ah... ah... ah... ah...
If the voices were easier to understand, I could go back to being easier to understand.
I don't know.
What? Uncle Dan?
Is he big?
Uncle big?
Oh, he's big!
Big? Big, big, big.
Oh!
One, two, three...
No, no, no.
That's not what I was expecting.
I thought you were one of those people who wandered into the same world as me.
You're the only one that's been acting weird... since the last time I saw you.
It's not like there's something wrong with this road.
I wonder if there's something else wrong with him.
Gnawing.
What, Uncle?
No, nothing's changed. There's no uncle.
And the posters.
No, he hasn't changed.
One camera in operation.
No change.
Underground plaza
Power distribution room
For business staff only
Cleaners.
What? No change?
Well, I've come all the way to 3, so I'll be a little sad if it's different now.
But if it's different, I don't know what's changed.
Oh, my...
Oh, here it is! I'm up to four... here it comes!
Yes!
I didn't think it would work.
It's going to be quick, isn't it?
I don't know what "kachan" is.
There's a wide-angle camera.
There's a golden circle.
Poster, Uncle
My hair has turned red.
Not so much.
Nothing? Nothing has changed.
The poster hasn't changed either?
I guess so.
No, it hasn't changed.
No, it hasn't changed. I don't think so.
Already 5! That's fast, fast, fast!
I think it's going to be 8.
No smoking
What?
It hasn't changed again.
Is it faster? Did you walk faster? Not at all?
And the poster.
I wonder if they even change that little number.
No, but they haven't changed.
The forecamera is still working.
The distribution room hasn't changed.
Underground plaza
Unchanged.
Fire hydrant.
How can it be the same?
What's that?
You're kidding?
The cab hasn't changed.
What?
The underground plaza.
There's something here. Where?
Where's...
Mister? I knew it.
I should notice every little change in him?
Like, I should notice if he's changing his mind?
Like, what's on your uncle's mind right now?
I don't know anything about that.
I agree with you.
I'm sorry.
What, if we were starting from scratch, would this be any different?
Uncle
Uncle happy face
There are posters.
Security camera in operation.
It's a distribution room, right?
For employees only.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
From here? From here?
Oh, it's one! That's good, that's good, that's good!
One more?
Yes, sir.
No smoking.
Hey, Uncle Dan.
looks the same
Lilithy face as usual
and the poster hasn't changed either
distribution room
Oh, yeah?
Turn back... turn back...
Scary, scary.
What?
Turn back.
What? If there's something wrong, we'll turn back, right? Is it okay to turn back? If we follow the instructions...
Oh, Uncle! You're my brother! I see you!
What's wrong?
Do you get lost a lot? You're lost too.
Oh, yeah, that's the thing. I have to turn around.
What? What? Change?
Mosmoking, posters 4, 5, 6.
He hasn't changed. Neither has Pops.
No makeover? No, he hasn't.
There's a practice room.
Oh, my God!
There's someone in there!
Oh, I'm scared.
There's an employee. No, there's an employee.
No, there's an employee. There's an employee.
Oh, Mister. Oh, scary.
Someone was peeking between us. Scary!
Scary!
Eh, what?
Does it have a zoom function? I want to zoom, I want to zoom
Can I get close to this thing? Oh, this is weird.
I don't know how far I can go with this. Good morning.
Good morning, sir.
Is there such a thing as death by touch?
It's beautiful.
No, this is first class.
First class, the way you divide it.
I'm gonna go take a look at this.
The Shining
It's like The Shining.
Uncle Shining, double.
Can I walk past it and come out?
Can I walk past it and look at it?
Scary, scary, scary.
What? What? Huh? Huh?
Huh? Huh?
Huh? It's back.
Huh? I'm back.
I'm back to Prince Shining W.
Huh?
What? Does that mean I'm back to zero?
You can go back to zero.
He killed me.
W killed me.
What?
Wow, that's one of the scariest things I've ever seen.
That's twice in a row I've been scared.
I wonder if there are any details on the poster, Uncle.
Looks the same.
Makeup Move Fest security cameras.
Near Plaza?
Can I?
What, what, what, what, what, why, why, why did I get hit by this, this is strange, I can't see it, I can't see it
What? Where is it? Where is it? Where is it?
I was so surprised that you also put A waterworks on the shelf...
Wow, what a surprise! Lighting problem!
I guess that's how it happens
Wow, what a surprise!
ah ah ah ah ah ah
Shining
I can't be killed anymore. I can't be killed anymore.
Aah!
I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared
No, no, no, no
Aah! Aah! Aah! Aah! Aah! Aah!
It's too close.
It's okay, just a little bit.
No, it's okay, just a little bit.
You're too hard on him.
I think it's the other way around.
It doesn't look the same.
This is strange.
Just 5 more 5 more 5 more and we'll be at Exit 8.
What?
I think there's something in there.
What? It's a fuselage.
It's a fuselage.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, help!
Oh, here it comes, here it comes.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Oh, wait, where is it? Where is it?
Heh heh heh heh heh heh.
What, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what...
He kissed me, he kissed me.
Heh heh heh heh heh...
I just got kissed
He pushed me against the wall and kissed me
Oh, oh, oh, oh
I'm scared
I'm not used to using a controller, so I can't escape.
Zero.
Can we get out of this?
There's stairs.
Oh, zero. What?
Where are we going once we get up here?
What? We should turn around.
I want to go up!
You can go up!
I'll go up.
Even if we die.
I'll have a bright future ahead of me.
Huh?
Hmm?
Ah.
I was hallucinating. I was hallucinating.
Well, that's because we have to go out of Exit 8.
It's the same. It looks the same.
Llam llam llam llam llam llam llam llam llam.
I don't think it's changed.
I don't think it's changing.
Oh!
Where is it?
Mmm-hmm.
What? Where?
Where?
This place has changed.
Please tell me.
What's wrong? What's wrong?
What's wrong? It's different, isn't it?
Oh, my God!
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Oh, the door's gone. I'm stepping on it. It's gone.
Oh, okay, okay, okay. Almost there, almost there. Almost there.
Almost there, but it's hard to tell.
There's nothing on the floor. Six gold circles, six posters.
There is a door.
Uncle Vova, you have a serious face.
Is it the same?
He looks the same.
Where?
Where is it?
Not so much.
Uncle, it's your uncle.
Where's your uncle?
Did you change the color of your socks?
That's enough.
Oh, my God.
What?
I don't know what's different.
Nothing's changed.
Is it the width of the floor or something?
Mister...
So, we have 6 posters.
I wonder if they'll change the smallest part of the room.
And there's a distribution board room
For business staff only.
Oh! What? What?
What?
Can I come in here?
No?
Ha!
I just said the end myself.
This place is open. We have cleaners here.
There were some employees here earlier, but you know how lonely they can be.
The city.
The floor is fine, the width is fine, the corridor is fine, there's even a money smoker at exit 8.
Six posters.
Buntenkan, Oji.
He's smiling.
Did something good happen? Did something good happen?
Cute! I want to take a picture of this. I can't take a picture.
Oh, cute! He's smiling.
He's got an archaic smile.
He's smiling. He's smiling.
I love it when he doesn't change.
I feel like I haven't changed.
Oh, thank goodness he hasn't changed.
I'm going to Exit 4.
Oh, no.
"Kim Monkey.
I want to take exit 8.
Exit 8.
I want to go to 8
Mister.
It hasn't changed.
The distribution board room.
The posters haven't changed either.
Oh,
The door...
That's the door knob.
It's the position of the doorknob.
Here it is! Here it is! Here it is!
Here it is!
Mr. Uncle!
Almost there! Almost there!
Almost there!
What's wrong?
It's different, isn't it?
And the poster.
Oh? Is the poster bigger?
What? Is it longer?
Oh, it's grown.
Oh, it's getting longer?
It's growing.
Oh, wow.
Oh, my gosh! It's an aha experience.
I wonder how big it will get if it stays here forever.
I wonder how big it's going to get.
What, am I gonna die?
Is the poster going to kill me? Oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God.
It's going to get bigger and bigger! Wow, it's so easy to see.
Great, I'm coming back. Oh, thank God!
Oh, my God, it's getting bigger and bigger. The poster's getting bigger and bigger.
Almost there, almost there! Here it comes! And a little bit more of that!
Here it comes!
And...
The floor hasn't changed. No smoking.
The posters haven't gotten any bigger. Pops?
Pops hasn't changed.
Wow, this place.
The ceiling? I don't know.
Some kind of stain? I don't remember seeing spots like this.
Looks like a face.
Is this a mutation?
There's a spot that looks like a face. I don't know if it's an anomaly.
I don't think it was here before.
Here.
I'll go back.
I'll be shocked if it's not.
Oh! What is it?
What is it?
One more to go. Exit 8.
Wow, that's not so easy to find.
Oh, no...
Fuji hasn't changed... and 6 posters.
And two more here. Underground plaza.
What? Fuji hasn't changed.
No change...
I don't think it's changed.
I wonder if it's still the same at the end.
Ah! Oh! What?
The end?
Here it comes!
Exit 8!
What? Does this mean it's over?
Does this mean we're done?
Does this mean we're leaving?
What?
Does that mean we have one more?
What? What? What? Huh?
Huh? Huh?
That's not good.
Six hemp posters.
You're still the same dandy.
Dandy as ever!
Here in the distribution board room
Underground plaza
It won't open.
Fire line.
What?
Huh?
Heh heh heh.
Yeah, it's moving really fast.
It's moving so much.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
It's moving so much! Scary. Something's wrong. There's something wrong.
There's something wrong.
There's an exit.
What is this? Is this really number 8? It's really exit 8.
Exit 8.
Is this different from before? It was zero.
Can I go now? Can I go?
Go!
Is it out?
Is it coming?
Oh, it's done!
Oh, we're out!
We made it out.
Exactly one hour. It took seven hours.
But this game says 15 minutes to an hour, so if you're fast, it'll be a lot faster.
I think that when you come to Tokyo, you often have to ride the underground passageway or subway.
I'll be careful about the Yawata exit from now on.
Thank you for watching!
Please subscribe to our channel and give us a high rating!